<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Masood&#39;s Digital Space</title>
    <link>https://masoodazizi.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Masood&#39;s Digital Space</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:07:32 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://masoodazizi.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Leo Turns One: The Reality of First-Time Dog Ownership</title>
      <link>https://masoodazizi.com/leo-turns-one-the-reality-of-first-time-dog-ownership/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2025 20:07:32 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://masoodazizi.com/leo-turns-one-the-reality-of-first-time-dog-ownership/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://masoodazizi.com/images/blog-post-cover-leo-first-year.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Leo: Our Maltipoo Dog&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Beyond the tech world that often consumes our daily lives, there are unique experiences that profoundly enrich us. Today marks a special milestone: &lt;strong&gt;our dog Leo&amp;rsquo;s first birthday&lt;/strong&gt;. Reflecting on the past nine months since we welcomed him into our home, I want to share my personal experience—one that is shaped by my own characteristics, emotions, and challenges.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I acknowledge that dog ownership is a subjective journey; each person’s experience will differ based on their lifestyle, temperament, and prior experience with pets. For my wife and me, Leo is our first dog, and we were completely inexperienced. Our journey is one from an amateur&amp;rsquo;s perspective, filled with learning curves, surprises, and valuable lessons.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Build and Publish a Personal Website</title>
      <link>https://masoodazizi.com/how-to-build-and-publish-a-personal-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2025 18:38:00 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://masoodazizi.com/how-to-build-and-publish-a-personal-website/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://masoodazizi.com/images/how-to-publish-personal-site.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;How to Build and Publish a Personal Website&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In today’s digital world, having a personal professional website is a valuable asset for showcasing your expertise, experiences, and achievements. A personal website not only provides a centralized platform to highlight your skills but also helps you build a strong online presence. For professionals, it serves as a modern-day business card—an easily accessible portfolio that reflects your personality and expertise.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I decided to create my own website, &lt;strong&gt;Masood&amp;rsquo;s Digital Space&lt;/strong&gt;, to:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to My Blog</title>
      <link>https://masoodazizi.com/welcome-to-my-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jan 2025 17:04:09 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://masoodazizi.com/welcome-to-my-blog/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://masoodazizi.com/images/welcome.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Welcome to My Blog - Masood&amp;rsquo;s Digital Space&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hello, and welcome to my digital home!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m Masood Azizi, a Cloud Architect passionate about designing scalable, secure, and innovative solutions in the cloud. With years of experience in AWS, DevOps, and security, this space is where I share insights, lessons, and experiences from my journey in tech.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here’s what you can expect:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tech Insights&lt;/strong&gt;: Exploring cloud architecture, DevSecOps, and automation.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Career Stories&lt;/strong&gt;: Sharing experiences from my professional journey.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Resources and Tips&lt;/strong&gt;: Practical guides and tools for navigating the world of cloud computing.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This site is a space to connect, learn, and grow together. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a tech enthusiast, a professional looking to level up your skills, or just curious about the cloud, there’s something here for you.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
